There is a man under the gallery there. I mean under the gallery somewhere there.
You ordered for the talisman from a foreign country. Ring, handkerchief but that came to you.
You used it for several, and later it disappeared.
Well, I don't know. The repercussion of it - you have seen it.
So come. Jesus loves you. He is there.
Prophecy Confirmation
My name is Former Doctor Buh Ignatius from Cameroon.
I am the one to confirm the prophesy of the Man of God, that there is a man who commanded a ring two years ago;
and the ring disappeared so the repercussion is now on his children and his life.
My children are here.
This is a talisman.This is a completion of the book to confirm what the Man of God said.
Testimony Time
Good morning, church.
My name is Spiritual Doctor Buh Ignatius from Cameroon.
The woman standing beside me is my wife.
I am here to confirm the prophesy of Man of God last Sunday.
He said there is a man under the gallery; he pointed directly to me;
who commanded a ring from oversea and handkerchief and a book.
And now there is repercussion. He should come out, his life is in danger.
So I never wanted to come out. I don't know what brought me out,
until I found myself in front of the altar.
So the prophecy of the Man of God was 100% true.
I have the book here with me.
So all this started some 28 years ago.
I was not fortunate to be born in a Christian home.
My grandfather was a high priest in my village, while my father was an occultist.
So I grew up from that background.
At the age of 14, I was in Secondary school. The strange ailment occurred to me.
They were running helter-skelter for my treatment.
But to no avail. So after three months of sickness my grandfather ordered my father to bring me
to the village. I went to the village for treatment.
So I was there. I stayed there for some months. In the course of the treatment my grandfather died.
Two weeks after the burial, some certain old people came.
The least of them was at least 75 years.
They said, my grandfather left a will, that I am the one to inherit him.
At that age of 14 years, I had no other options than to accept.
But I tried to talk with my father and ask him with my mother whether it is true.
They said it's true. They were prepared for that.
So from that moment, I had no option. My father came because my father was based in Boya by that time.
My village is some 500km from Boya. So I was there with my grandfather,
in the north west region; while my father was working in the south west region.
So they called for him. They came with my mother. They bought a goat and 7 traditional chickens.
So I was carried behind the house, the goat was slaughtered.
And I drunk the blood and I was in the river at midnight without clothes.
And they killed those chickens. They gave me 7 hearts of chickens to swallow.
So immediately I swallowed, things never became the same in my life again.
I became different. I became very violent. From that moment, a serious spirit of lust came to me.
As I started practicing; the first three months I had only four wives,
married officially. The first year I had already seven wives.
So I don't know what was happening.
So you started practicing as a witch doctor from the age of...
From the day of my introduction, they said I have no time to waste because my grandfather left a lot of jobs undone.
So how old were you then when you started practicing?
I was 14 years of age. So the initiation process took 4 years.
But that 4 years I was practicing while on initiation, because there was no other person.
I was the only one by that time.
At the age of 18 I was already full time witch doctor.
So people were coming from left and right all over the place to see me
because I am not only known in Cameroon but all over the world.
They were coming to see me.
But one faithful day, a general came and met me in the village and said - no,
my talent does not warrant me to be in the village.
That he wants to take me out. I consulted those old people, they said - no,
they are already old, I should go out and look for food for them.
So they allowed me to go to capital city in Yaounde.
So the general rented for me a four bedroom flat and lodged me there.
I was working for him. He was bringing other patients.
That is where I established myself in Yaounde becoming known now in Yaounde.
So from that time, things were moving very well as I can say.
Because people were coming from left and right.
Goods were there, cows, fowls everything.
People were healed, as I can say; but tomorrow there is a problem.
You are healed today, tomorrow there is problem.
You come back, I still give you another alternative -
to try to bring this the next day - just like that.
So by that time, I had varieties of clients but my principal clients were prostitutes
and armed robbers and fraudsters - they actually came to me to seek for my help.
As I say, I was a chief priest. So I usually gave them charms to destroy minds of people,
to confuse people. For example, a fraudster could come to me and say: "I have a client at United Arab Emirates,
I have been talking to him 2 years ago, we had a project for 2 billion."
I will ask to give me the name. You give me the name, I will work on it.
The man will accept everything and my percentage will come.
That's how I have been practicing until they carry me also out of the country to practice.
So I have been practicing all over with fraudsters.
And armed robber will come - he wants charm for gun shoot
above human destruction. I prepare charm for him, he will go, they will shoot him -
nothing will enter. And at times, we disappear, at times they will bring a robe of a dead corpse.
I will work on that robe, they will put it in people's compound.
You will sleep with your family and operate without any incident.
So that is how I been practicing. Those are my three main customers.
For over 28 years today. A woman can come to me and say: "I want a man."
I will ask whether she has a name of somebody. At times, it usually follows that he is a married man.
I have no option. I am there to do my job.
So I will be the first now to destroy that marriage first,
before implanting them as husband and wife.
That's how I usually practice. It was so common for me to do.
At that time I was only 11 years as a serious witch doctor in my country.
Unfortunate for me, my father who was supporting me spiritually, fell sick, he died.
So he left a will that I should not go with him in my village,
I should bury him 17 kilometers from wamy village. I asked why, he said he was trying to protect me and my brothers.
I said: "It is very difficult; you know, you will not be there.
I will not fight those people." He said he will be with me.
So I started the project until I buried my father 17 km as he said.
Returning now to my initiators, they never wanted to see me because,
my father owed debt from them, spiritual debts.
Yes. They wanted my father to be buried there, to use his corpse for certain things.
So of which he knew. He slided so I was a target now.
So they started following me. I was banned not to be again in their midst.
So I was stranded. In the midst of that confusion, one of my friends who attended the funeral of my father -
from West Africa, he was based in Ghana precisely - he came to Cameroon.
He condoled with me. He proposed to me to talk after the funeral.
We left now from the village to Boya. We talked very well. He said he would help me.
I was desperate because nobody was coming again, everything was down by that time.
I could not sleep, I could not rest. I didn't have with my wife... I could not meet as husband and wife.
And out I would have women doing things with them but with my wife - nothing.
Those seven women - nothing, only outside.
Having kids left and right - everything was down.
How did you manage to get these women?
Those women are patient, they usually come to me. When you are beautiful you will not go.
Like this one she is one of the victims beside me.
They came for consultation. They consulted me. Like this one came with a leg problem.
An ulcer. So by the power of darkness, I treated her. I said: "No, you will not go."
I just started like a joke, that was all. This is 14 years she has been with me.
The Ogugu power took them as slaves. The spirit took them as slaves for me.
She is a victim. The principal victim because...
Now tell us; you said you met a friend who promised to help you. What happened?
So as I met that friend, we finished the funeral of my father, we came to Boya.
That is where the prophecy of the man of God came in.
So by that time he said I should give my underwears, he will travel with it.
I took my underwears and gave to him. He left for Ghana.
But he had a contact with a particular high priest in China.
So he told me that he will not allow me to meet that high priest in personally.
Because the conditions are too heavy and the way he has seen me - I was depressed.
I could not bear it. He said he would work as a middle man for me.
So he took those underwears and went.
Two weeks after, I had a call that I should go to a T- junction -
where I discovered this book and a ring. Yes.
So at midnight I took this book and a ring and went with it.
At 2 am a person appeared to me and gave instruction that I should open page 24 -
I would see a brochure, I would read to get instructions. So I read everything.
They said I should look for a plate and a knife and a live dove.
So that dove was caught. I drank the blood, I swallow the heart.
Immediately a serious spirit of divination came to me.
That nobody can stand me by that time. I was above human destruction.
So as I went there, I met this book and a ring. A red-coloured ring.
And I took it and at 2am somebody appeared to me and gave me instruction
that I should open page 24, I would see a small paper, a brochure. I should read.
So I went through the instructions. They said I should buy a new plate and a knife and a live dove.
So to have that dove was not easy. The next day they directed me again
to go where I took this book and I found the dove waiting for me.
So I took the dove. I did not complain but within me I was complaining.
So they answered me because they knew my heart because I was already engaged with them.
That is it. So I went now, I collected that dove. The dove was slaughtered.
The dove was slaughtered and I drank the blood and I swallowed the heart.
Immediately a serious spirit of divination came to me.
I discovered that I am above human destruction. By that time I was not myself again.
A witch doctor in the past, now a spiritual leader; is just for treatment and to do atrocity
because nothing like that. God doesn't like that now that I am before the Arena of Liberty.
I am really regretting but in the past I was completely happy.
So I started doing things, performing miracles in my country, going abroad doing miracles.
Women were coming. Prostitutes were coming. I bounced back to form
because I was already weak when my initiator abandoned me.
So now as I received this, I became very strong and powerful that I needed not their help again.
I was now independent. Relying only on my friend giving him details about my performance.
For example, my principal customers were prostitutes; because in them
the condition they gave me, was that I will not sacrifice because my friend was already sacrificing human blood.
So for me I will not sacrifice. But virtues of people - I mean the manliness of people -
will be taken from prostitutes to the kingdom.
Yes. For more power. So prostitutes will act as a principal source of my spiritual revenue.
So that is it. Any person who patronized them is a victim to me.
Immediately you sleep with them, you are now in the kingdom.
After I meet a woman like that - two, three weeks, a month, two months - your activities will never be the same again.
You start accusing people left and right without knowing where your problems come from.
Without knowing we are the cause. So if you are a business man, you will never do business again.
If you are a civil servant, in your job site there will be problems left and right.
So those are the things that usually happen to those people.
I did this. At times, I usually had, let's say twenty thousand dollars in my hand;
the next day I will not have a franc. All those women, even to feed them was a problem.
Of which there is money entering everyday.
I don't know where the money was going. At this time, when I am talking now before the children of God,
I don't have where to go. My children are not going to school. I don't have a place to live.
All projects I have started have been stopped.
So to prove that, I was really in the world. If me, the master, could suffer like this -
they would have triple suffering, in their area.
So I feel sorry for them but by that time, I had no other option.
So this woman beside me did something... We are in the presence of God.
I went one day for an operation in one neighbouring village in Yaounde -
serious operation with a dignitary. I returned, I found she has installed a certain television in my house
called Emmanuel TV. As I entered the house, the whole house was not the same.
I asked her: "What happened?"
She said a cable man came into the house and installed a television.
She had been watching, it's very interesting.
Talking to me happily without knowing that I was already disturbed.
So I held my temper because there were people.
After they left she was seriously beaten and I warned her never to put that television again.
Because from that time, that very day, I started having problems with my sleep.
And those people started warning me that if I do not send this woman out, my life is in danger.
So I threw her out. As I threw her out, as she was already in an covenant with me - she could not be out.
She would come in again. I would still send her out, she would come in
because there was no way she could resist what we did in the beginning.
So you mean since the day your wife installed Emmanuel TV in your house
there has been no peace, that means you have been troubled because of your evil practices?
I have never got peace, until that day that I went to my shrine.
I found that my ring is no more there. The ring disappeared without any knowledge.
I looked for the ring. The next day I had the call.
Mr Buh Ignatius - Prophecy Testimony
Glory be to God! At this point in time, for the benefit of those who are just joining us,
viewers all over the world, this confession you are listening to was born out of a prophecy
given by the anointed Man of God last Sunday service to this man about a talisman
he received from a foreign country and a ring. The ring which he refers to right now
as having disappeared after the Emmanuel TV was installed in his house.
Can we refresh our memory again and for those who are just joining us to see what the prophecy spoke about,
what the man is talking about right now. Let's watch the screen again and see this prophecy.
Prophecy Time
There is a man under the gallery there, I mean under the gallery somewhere there.
You ordered for the talisman from a foreign country - ring, handkerchief.
But they came to you, you used it for several... and later it disappeared.
Well, I don't know. The repercussion of it - you have seen it.
So come. Jesus loves you. He is there.
Prophecy Confirmation
My name is former Doctor Buh Ignatius from Cameroon.
I am the one to confirm the prophecy of Man of God.
That there is a man who commanded the ring two years ago and the ring disappeared.
So the repercussion is now on his children and his life.
My children are here. This a talisman. This is a completion of the book to confirm what the Man of God said.
Ok, so tell us eventually, how did you find yourself at the SCOAN last week before this prophecy came.
It was not easy. The prophecy came, I stood there for over 5 minutes thinking back
how many patients count on me because my coming here was just for deliverance, to have rest
and to tap from the anointing of the Man of God to continue my job.
That was my aim coming here.
So you mean, your coming here last Sunday was to come and seek for breakthrough, for success
and to add more powers to the power you already had to practice your occultic and witch doctor practices.
But you didn't know that the power here was the power from above.
That is true. Brethren, children of God, my coming here was to have more power.
Because in the kingdom we know this man, the man at the Synagogue. We know him.
Because in the whole world - it is the only Prophet that talks love, peace and forgiveness and faith.
Others talk of money.
Mr Buh Ignatius - Prophecy Testimony
And those are things we forbid in the kingdom. We don't want to hear love, unity, faith and reconciliation.
So he is the only Prophet. If you hear most of his sermons, he never talks of wealth, prosperity.
Only faith, forgiveness - so he is the most hated Prophet in the kingdom.
So we know that there is anointing on him. So I came here to tap a bit to go now and perform more.
Ok. In those days, despite you knew that the Man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua is a prophet of God;
and his anointing is from above, you never realized what the Bible says - that
light and darkness have nothing in common.
I never realized because I have went to other places that this woman took me.
As I entered there; the next day we are friends with the pastor,
we eat and dine together. They come even for prophecy and give me names to prophecy for them.
So I thought this....
But when you came here, you were arrested.
I found a different story. I was exposed.
You say?..
I found a different story. I was exposed because I wanted just my deliverance, to rest, to sleep,
to have peace with my family and return now performing.
And you were exposed instead.
Exposed!
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus.
Truly, this the first time. I have been to places with this woman behind me, as I said,
carrying me everywhere. At times, I was going there to please her.
When I went there, I was delivered - they said it's over.
The next day I would have sexual intercourse with 20-30 women per night.
The next day after they said you are delivered, the pastor would call me and say:
"I want to see you privately." He would give some names to prophecy.
I would prophecy and write on a paper. When the people come, he will make the prophecy as if he is the one.
So I knew it was the style of life, so we were together.
Ok, so since last Sunday after the Man of God gave the prophecy you came out,
and you confirmed it and you were delivered. Can you tell us what are the evidences
of this deliverance in your life?
For many years till today I was suffering -
from this repercussion as the Man of God said.
This is the first week - last week that I have slept.
My children are resting because they didn't even sleep in the house.
They were always out sleeping on top of roofs. My wife - nobody could sleep.
We didn't have any rest. So it is the first time in my life for a long period that I sleep like a baby, and get up.
Until the woman that was in contact with me has not called me since Sunday last week.
She had a proposal for me to come in Cameroon in April for recruitment for youths,
for martyr. So she never called me since Sunday till today.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus.
And that anger that you used to have?
That anger is gone. I am now like a baby. That spirit of lust, that I can not be a day
without having sexual intercourse - I don't feel it.
And I am now a father, talking to my children, conversing with my wife. Making projects.
Even without any future, I know there is a God that will take me through.
Once again let's clap for Jesus Christ.
We thank God Almighty for the wonderful deliverance you have received.
The Bible says when Jesus Christ enters our lives, He puts an end to our past and gives birth to our future.
Now your past is over. Old things pass away, all things become new.
We give glory to God for your life.
Emmanuel! (God with us Matthew 1:23)
People of God, Emmanuel! (God with us Matthew 1:23).
My name is Anaba Marie Chantal. I come from Cameroon.
I am here today, because of the prophecy the Man of God gave to my husband.
I am francophone, I don't speak English but I can manage it.
I met this man through my friend. I have been having legs pain.
And I have been looking for a witch doctor - some person to treat my leg.
It's my friend introduced me to him. After that I have been having a rich man, the man who was supposed to marry me.
But I don't know what happened. I didn't want to see the man again.
I liked only him. I rejected the man. I wanted only him.
He had three wives, and I was number four.
People of God, I was suffering a lot because that man beside me, a witch doctor had very violent spirit.
He was beating me, he could burn you with the iron, he could knock you with the stick.
He could do anything but you could not say anything to him.
If he brought a woman in front of you - you could not say anything.
If he was meeting a woman behind you - you could not say anything.
If you opened your mouth, he would beat you seriously and you could not do anything to him.
If he beat me today and I left the house, my heart would be beating me like this that if I didn't come back to him,
I would die.
So you mean, even with the beating that you used to receive from this man,
you could not stay outside the home for one day without coming back to the house.
Why is it that you always found yourself coming back to the house?
Because you are inside the charm and the charm controls you.
After that I took in, I have one boy with him. Since 13-14 years, I gave birth to only one child for him.
I never took in again. And other ladies, outside ladies - they would bring the child of 2-3 years.
He would just give you like that - you are the one who is supposed to look after that child.
He brought another one of 9 months - you are the one supposed to look after that child
and take it just like that - I could not argue.
I just took the child, I could not refuse because if you try he will be beating you until...
With all the beating you could not go?
Yes, I could not run. As I went out , the next day I would come back inside my house.
Ok, your husband said he used to have different people coming to consult him.
He would do charm for them like many prostitutes, arm robbers.
So those prostitutes that used to come visit him, what did he used to do with them?
The moment I came to the house of juju, we started making them medicine. I was seeing women, men standing in a big line like this.
They were having fowls, goats, ducks. They were cutting all these things, taking their blood and putting it
inside the water. They were bathing people mixing it with perfume.
After that I would give them charm
to go stealing, doing... That one that wanted to travel, go about - we were doing all the charms for the people.
Then after that, the moment that you came back to the house - this moment he could love you.
But when the spirit came, he would start beating without any reason.
You could do any small thing - he did not allow you, he would beat you.
Beating from him, prostitutes... He could sleep with woman beside you.
He did not have any remorse. He could not even change.
He could not do anything, where he would please you or beg you.
He would do anything that his heart told him. That's all.
Marie Chantal - Prophecy Testimony
Ok, you mean all this while when your husband received these different women,
he would carry them to your matrimonial bed in your presence, and you could not say anything?
It's true.
If you challenged him, he would beat you.
He would beat you. You could not challenge him, you could not say anything to him - he would beat you.
He would do what he wanted to do. That is it.
And after I delivered my child, I could not have sexual relation with him again
because if he wanted to come to me, his skin would be weak.
But in the night I was seeing him physically making love with me.
In the dream?
In the dream.
In the dream. He could meet you in the dream as a husband but physically he could not again.
He could not , yes.
He would become weak, whenever he came to you.
Yes.
After that I started seeing a child sucking my breast, having sexual relationship with him in the dream.
Ok, since your husband's deliverance last Sunday, can you tell us what are the changes you have seen in him.
After last Sunday, the Man of God prophesied to my husband. I said: "Oh!"
Because I knew, all these things we were passing through - there is a God.
I knew that the God who saved me, must take me through.
And last Sunday, I saw the Man of God prophesying to him. I said: "Hallelujah."
That my suffering has ended today.
Ok, so tell us what are the things that have changed in the life of your husband,
since after the prophecy and deliverance last Sunday.
Yes, Man of God.
So what are the things you noticed now - those things he used to do before?
Tell us, what of now after his deliverance?
Since that deliverance on Sunday my husband behaves normal.
He can not go behind answering the call. He is sitting in the house, no more shouting.
He is quiet. He can not go out. He is no longer looking up and down for women.
He is quiet now.
He is very quiet now in the house since the Man of God prophesied to him on Sunday.
He is very quiet. I feel peace now. I look at myself and say that I am a human being now.
Because before he would look at me and ask me: "What are you doing here?"
And he would beat you everyday, do anything he wanted.
"You are not going. What are you doing here? I want different women, I don't want to see you again in this house.
What are you doing here?" I had to look like this.
I was not doing anything, because I knew that I could not go. He knew where he put me in.
I didn't know anything. But now I am a woman.
You are a woman now?
Yes.
You too are delivered now.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus.
So the the first time you installed Emmanuel TV in your house, you say,
your husband came, he saw it and he beat you.
Yes. The day that I discovered Emmanuel TV - this man wanted to kill me that day.
But through Emmanuel TV now, God delivered him.
Yes. And through Emmanuel TV now he has the deliverance.
Hallelujah! Let us clap for Jesus Christ.
So now your eyes are opened, unlike before when you didn't know where you were,
you didn't know you were in a cage as a result of the charm your husband had charmed you
when you met him as a witch doctor. Now your husband is delivered, you are delivered.
How do you see him now?
I am very happy to see him because I know that his behavior was not normal.
Now I fall in love with him again. I see my husband as my husband now.
Marie Chantal Prophecy Testimony
I know that before he was not my husband because that first time I was married "na juju".
Because he was not behaving like a man, a human being.
But now he is changed, this is my husband now.
So with what you have passed through, your experience, your level in the occultic world
and now you are delivered, looking back at where you are coming from -
what advice do you have for people who are listening to your testimony now
and for those who are still engaged in that occultic practice out there?
What word of advice do you have for them?
My advice will go first to parents. I was not fortunate to grow in a Christian home,
Any parent because of his selfish ambitions and selfish projects should not include his children into it.
Because my father put me to this thing without my knowledge. That's the first for parents.
Secondly, for my colleagues all over the world, they are watching me now. I know.
Because if the head has fallen, it means everybody must succumb.
It's time that we must put our arms down to focus, to know the truth, for the truth to set us free.
The truth has been hidden for so long but this is the day that I, Buh Ignatius,
am standing before the whole world talking that I am tired. I have tried the other side.
For a week now, I have tried this side, I have tested it - it's reliable.
So they should change.
God is reliable.
TT Monica Asefa 20/08/18
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 28/08/2018